

PROFILE

I am a youthful AI engineer, researcher and robotics developer. Programming and working with computers in general has been a passion for quite some time.

In love with automation and minimizing repetitive work, which is why I'm able to focus on efficient & application-oriented learning, developing and problem solving.

Switching views, working on agile projects and changing approaches often motivate me to study new topics, tackle hard challenges and deliver results.

BIRTHDATE 11 januari 2000

ADDRESS

Houthalen-Helchteren, Belgium

PHONE NUMBER +32486539354

MAILING ADDRESS kobethuwis26@gmail.com

KOBE THUWIS

EDUCATION

2018-2021: Hogeschool PXL

Bachelor in Applied Information Technology with a specialisation in Artificial Intelligence (AI) & robotics.

2012-2018: Kindsheid Jesu

High school diploma in Maths & Sciences

EXPERIENCE

PXL Smart ICT: Research & Development Intern 2021 - Present

ArtiFISHal Intelligence is a twofold project, consisting of scenes made in Unity which illustrate several reinforcement learning techniques. Secondly, the project contains a simulation of a marine ecosystem which uses state of the art evolutionary algorithms.

Chiro Meulenberg: Head Monitor 2019 - Present

The head monitor is responsible for the entire group and is often required to make democratic decisions and lead others were needed. Chiro Meulenberg is a youth movement counting more than 250 active members.

Strandbal: Event Manager 2018 - Present

Strandbal is a small event / festival in Houthalen-Helchteren. The profit of Strandbal is used to fund the workings of Chiro Meulenberg. Strandbal is one of the bigger youth-events in Houthalen: 2000+ youngsters visit the event every year!

Youth Council Member 2019 - Present

As a member of the youth council I am involved in local politics and youth counseling in Houthalen-Helchteren.

PORTFOLIO

https://kobethuwis.github.io/

Make sure to visit my portfolio to view any previous projects, skills and relevant experience!